	
 
 
What’s happening

 
Toys 'R' Us is reportedly preparing to close all of its US stores
Business ⋅ Earlier today
According to news reports, the toy chain is planning to liquidate its assets in the US amid bankruptcy. The store, wh...
Go to Moment	
 
Nigerian street artist's speed portraits become a viral sensation
Cool ⋅ 1 hour ago
When Sulayman Abu-bakr (@NupeMufasa) told the story of an artist he met outside his office, others from around Nigeri...
Go to Moment	
 
The Wire ended 10 years ago
Television ⋅ 41 minutes ago
Fans of the HBO crime drama are paying tribute to the iconic show, which many consider among the greatest television ...
Go to Moment	
 
Zendaya's performance in The Greatest Showman inspires tattoo
Celebrity ⋅ 3 hours ago
After falling in love with The Greatest Showman, @KaylaKouts decided to get started on a tattoo inspired by the movie...
Go to Moment	
 
Michael Smith is leaving SportsCenter
Sports newss ⋅ 5 hours ago
Just one month after his co-host Jemele Hill left, Michael Smith is parting ways with ESPN's SC6. Smith will make his...
Go to Moment	
 
This cat is named Dog and he sells fish
Animals ⋅ 4 hours ago
Phuong Le (@smallnartless) posted a photo of a stylish cat who works at a fish market in Vietnam and people can't get...
Go to Moment	
Settings  |  Help  |  Unsubscribe
We sent this email to @never0041
 	Twitter, Inc. 1355 Market Street, Suite 900 San Francisco, CA 94103