	
 
 
What’s happening

 
Tragic wreck kills two children and critically injures Broadway actress
US news ⋅ 2 hours ago
A deadly crash in Brooklyn, New York, killed Lauren Lew's one-year-old son, as well as four-year-old Abigail, who is ...
Go to Moment	
 
Bachelor Nation has questions about the ethics behind Arie's decision
Television ⋅ 5 hours ago
🚨 THIS MOMENT CONTAINS SPOILERS 🚨 Reality show alumni and fans are calling out the show for allowing "the first com...
Go to Moment	
 
Meet the richest people on the planet
Forbes ⋅ 5 hours ago
Announcing the 2018 Forbes Billionaires list: 2,208 billionaires from 72 countries and territories that are worth a c...
Go to Moment	
 
The San Francisco exodus is creating a U-Haul shortage
Business Insider ⋅ 2 hours ago
More residents are leaving San Francisco than any other US city. For as expensive as it is to live in San Francisco, ...
Go to Moment	
 
Investigation finds Kellyanne Conway violated Hatch Act by politicking for Roy Moore
Politics ⋅ 1 hour ago
The Hatch Act bans federal employees from partisan lobbying. The Office of Special Counsel determined that two of Kel...
Go to Moment	
 
What's The Greatest 3 Album Run Of All Time in Hip Hop?
evan auerbach ⋅ 2 hours ago
The title is clear enough: the best 3-consecutive rap album runs. The only guidelines are: no live albums, no greates...
Go to Moment	
Settings  |  Help  |  Unsubscribe
We sent this email to @never0041
 	Twitter, Inc. 1355 Market Street, Suite 900 San Francisco, CA 94103